
 [
  {
    "question": "A military commander exercising civil power by force, usually in a limited area",
    "choice1": "warlord",
    "choice2": "aristocrat",
    "choice3": "ancestor",
    "choice4": "pictograph",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "A member of an upper class of society, usually made of hereditary nobility",
    "choice1": "warlord",
    "choice2": "aristocrat",
    "choice3": "ancestor",
    "choice4": "pictograph",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "A person that someone is descended from ",
    "choice1": "warlord",
    "choice2": "aristocrat",
    "choice3": "ancestor",
    "choice4": "pictograph",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "A symbol in a writing system based on pictures",
    "choice1": "warlord",
    "choice2": "aristocrat",
    "choice3": "ancestor",
    "choice4": "pictograph",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "A symbol in a writing system that represents a thing or an idea",
    "choice1": "ideograph",
    "choice2": "aristocrat",
    "choice3": "ancestor",
    "choice4": "pictograph",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "A group of non-elected government officials",
    "choice1": "Dao",
    "choice2": "bureaucracy",
    "choice3": "ancestor",
    "choice4": "pictograph",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Having title or possession by reason of birth",
    "choice1": "Dao",
    "choice2": "Shang",
    "choice3": "hereditary",
    "choice4": "pictograph",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "The belief that the Chinese Kings right to rule came from the gods. ",
    "choice1": "Dao",
    "choice2": "Shang",
    "choice3": "warlord",
    "choice4": "Mandate of Heaven",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Chinese system of beliefs which describes the way a king must rule",
    "choice1": "Dao",
    "choice2": "Shang",
    "choice3": "pictograph and ideograph",
    "choice4": "pictures and symbols",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The first cities in China were built by ____ ",
    "choice1": "Dao",
    "choice2": "Shang",
    "choice4": "pictures and symbols",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "The ancient Chinese wrote in ____ ",
    "choice1": "chinese",
    "choice2": "English",
    "choice3": "pictograph and ideograph",
    "choice4": "pictures and symbols",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "The Zhou Dynasty developed _____________  to help increase farmland.",
    "choice1": "Mandate of Heaven",
    "choice2": "English",
    "choice3": "warlord",
    "choice4": "irrigation",
    "answer": 4
  }
]
